Guys, look! Ugly Naked Guy's
putting stuff in boxes.
얘들아, 벌거숭이 사내가
짐을 싸고 있어
I'd say our naked buddy is moving.
이사 갈 모양이네
Ironically, most of the boxes
seem to be labeled "Clothes."
희한하게 상자마다
'옷'이라고 적혔어
I'm going to miss that big
old squishy butt.
저 촉촉한 엉덩이가
그리울 거야
And we're done
with the chicken fried rice.
치킨 볶음밥은 다 먹었다
그래, 저 남자 이사 가면
내가 저기로 들어가면 되겠다
If he's moving, maybe I should
try to get his place!
- 좋은 생각이야
- 그래
It would be so cool
to live across from you guys.
너희랑 가까이 살면 좋잖아
그럼 전화놀이도 할 수 있고
We could do that telephone thing...
알지? 너 깡통 하나
우리도 깡통 하나
...where you have a can,
we have a can...
실로 연결하는 거 있잖아
...and it's connected by a string.
Or we could do
the actual telephone thing.
아니면 진짜 전화로 하든지
He's got packing tape stuck
to where you really don't want it.
포장테이프 갖고
요상한 짓한다
Get it off, fat man! Get it off!
그만둬, 그만두라고!
Oh, no, he's trying to pull it off slowly.
이런, 천천히 떼려고 하네
Take it from me, if you're gonna pull tape
off yourself, it's gotta be in one quick motion.
저렇게 하는 게 아냐
한방에 뜯어내야지
Like that.
저거야!
The One Where Everyone Finds Out
Oh, my God. I love this apartment!
세상에, 진짜 맘에 든다
완벽하지 않아?
Isn't it perfect?
I can't believe I never realized
how great it is!
이 집이 이렇게 좋았다니
벌거숭이 사내한테만
눈길이 쏠렸으니까
Because your eye goes
to the big naked man.
It's amazing!
멋지다
Hurry up with an application,
or I'll beat you to it.
빨리 입주신청서 작성해라
나한테 맞기 전에
Well, I'm going to use
Ugly Naked Guy's bathroom.
살다보니 이런 날도 있구나
벌거숭이 화장실 좀 써야겠다
Look! There's Monica and Chandler.
모니카랑 챈들러 보인다
얘들아!
얘들아, 나 봐라!
Hey, you guys!
왜 그래?
Chandler and Monica!
챈들러랑 모니카가!
세상에
Oh, my God!
- 챈들러랑 모니카!
- 엄마야!
Oh, my eyes!
내 눈! 내 눈이!
My eyes!
피비, 피비
괜찮아, 진정해
It's okay!
-They're doing it!
-I know!
아냐, 쟤들 사고 치잖아!
알아, 나도 안다니까
-I know!
-You know?
- 알아?
- 그래, 나랑 조이는 알지만
Yes, I know it. Joey knows,
but Ross doesn't, so stop screaming!
로스는 모르니까
소리 그만 질러!
What's going on?
무슨 일이야?
뭔데? 왜 그래?
-What?
-Nothing!
아냐, 네가 이 아파트
얻는다니까 너무 신난다
We are so excited
that you'll get this apartment!
Looks really good.
정말 괜찮지?
Looks pretty good!
아무렴! 좋고말고!
Get in here!
Come on!
너도 이리 와
모니카랑 챈들러가
빨래하러 간다거나
You mean whenever
Monica and Chandler...
...were doing laundry
or going grocery shopping?
뭐 사러 갔던 게 전부 다?
The time Monica spent on the phone
with Linda from camp?
린다랑 종일 전화했던 것도?
그럼, 당연하지
전화든 뭐든
Doing it, doing it, phone, doing it.
I can't believe it!
이럴 수가
정말 잘됐다
챈들러한테는
I think it's great. For him.
She could do better.
사실 모니카가 아깝지
Hey, you guys.
- 얘들아
- 조이, 이리 와봐
Come here!
뭔데?
Phoebe found out
about Monica and Chandler.
모니카랑 챈들러
피비한테도 들켰어
You mean how they're friends
and nothing more?
둘이 친구 이상은
아니라는 거?
아니...
피비도 안다니까
Joey, she knows.
We saw them doing it
through the window.
벌거숭이 집에서 보니까 둘이
창가에서 일을 저지르더라고
Actually, we saw them doing it
up against the window.
정확히 말하면 창에
밀어붙이고 하더라
간통현장을 붙잡았지롱
We saw them fornicating.
걔들은 조이가 아는 건 알고
레이첼이 아는 건 모른다고?
So they know you know,
and they don't know that Rachel knows?
Yes, but it doesn't matter
who knows what.
그래, 누가 뭘 아는지는
중요하지 않아
Now enough of us know
that we could just tell them we know.
이젠 우리가 다 안다는 걸
걔들한테 말해주자고
All the lying and the secrets
will finally be over.
그럼 거짓말과 비밀은
사라지는 거야
Or, we could not tell them we know,
and have a little fun.
아니면 알려주지 말고
우리끼리 재미 좀 보든지
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이야?
If they say they are doing laundry,
we'll give them laundry to do.
걔들이 빨래하러 간다고 하면
빨랫감을 한 아름 안겨주자고
- 그거 재미있겠다
- 아냐
I would enjoy that.
You know what would be even more fun?
Telling them.
잠깐, 이게 더 신나
말하는 거야
-That doesn't sound like fun.
-So we'll make it fun.
- 그건 재미없잖아
- 그래
재미있게 하면 되지
예를 들면...
We'll do it like a barbershop quartet!
4중창으로
We know, we know, we know
다 안다, 다 알아
다 압니다...
- 피비 생각이 더 낫다
- 난 더 이상...
No, I want to do Phoebe's thing.
I can't take
넌 그냥 우리가
안다는 것만 말하지 마
You don't have to do anything.
Just don't tell them we know.
싫어, 이제 비밀은
사양하고 싶어
I can't take anymore secrets.
I got your secrets, their secrets,
secrets of my own.
너희들 비밀에 걔네들 비밀
게다가 내 비밀까지 있다고
You don't have any secrets.
- 댁한테 무슨 비밀이 있나?
- 얼라려?
Well, you don't know about Hugsy,
my bedtime penguin pal.
내가 껴안고 자는
헉시라는 펭귄 알아?
그럼, 크흠!
How are we going to mess with them?
어떻게 골려주지?
넌 룸메이트라는
입장을 활용하고
You could use your position
as the roommate.
난 내가 쓸 수 있는
가장 강력한 무기를 쓰겠어
And I would use the strongest tool
at my disposal.
My sexuality.
관능미라고
Hello, children.
안녕, 얘들아
- 어서 와라
- 그래
좋아, 보고 잘 배워
내 과자는 먹지 말고
Watch. Learn.
And don't eat my cookie.
- 왔어?
- 그래
That jacket looks great on you.
그 재킷 정말 잘 어울린다
-Really?
-The material is so soft.
- 정말?
- 응, 촉감도 부드럽고...
Hello, Mr. Bicep.
안녕, 미스터 알통?
You're working out?
너 요새 운동하니?
뭐 힘은 좀 주고 있지
I try to squeeze things.
Are you okay?
너 괜찮니?
If you really want to know
정말 알고 싶다면...
아냐, 말 못해
I can't tell you this.
You can tell me anything.
나한테 못할 말이 뭐가 있어
사실 너니까 못하는 거야
Actually, you are the one person
I can't tell this to.
알아주기를 간절히
바라고는 있지만
And the one person I want to the most.
What's going on?
무슨 말이야?
나 남자 사귄 지
꽤 오래됐거든
I just haven't been
with a guy in so long...
...and sometimes you're
looking for something...
애타게 찾던 사람이 눈앞에서
커피를 마셔도 모를 때가 있지
...and it's right there
in front of you, sipping coffee....
Oh, no. Have I said too much?
내가 너무 많은 걸 밝혔나?
생각 좀 해볼게
잘될 거야
Just something to think about.
I know I will.
어머
You are so cute.
자긴 너무 귀여워
어쩌면 그렇게 귀여워?
How did you get to be so cute?
할아버지가 스웨덴 분이지
My grandfather was Swedish.
And my grandmother was
a tiny little bunny.
할머니는 조그만 토끼셨고
Now you're even cuter.
그러니깐 더 귀엽잖아
요즘은 다들 그렇게
생각하는 것 같아
You know, that is a popular
opinion today, I must say.
뭐?
오늘 커피하우스에서
묘한 일이 있었어
The weirdest thing happened
at the coffeehouse.
피비가 날 좋아하나 봐
Phoebe was hitting on me.
What are you talking about?
무슨 소리야?
피비한테는 내가
그렇게 멋져 보이나?
I think Phoebe thinks I'm foxy.
It's not possible.
말도 안 돼
미안해
I'm sorry, Phoebe's just
always thought you were charming...
피비가 널 좋아하긴 하지만
남자로 보진 않을 거야
...in a sexless kind of way.
감이 잘 안 오는데
You know, I can't hear that enough.
I just think you misunderstood her.
자기가 오해한 거겠지
오해가 아냐
아주 노골적이더라고
I didn't, okay?
She was all over me.
내 알통까지 만졌다니까
She touched my bicep,
for crying out loud.
This bicep?
이 알통?
Well, it's not flexed right now.
지금은 힘을 안 줘서 그래
Why is it so hard for you to believe
that Phoebe could be attracted to me?
피비가 나한테 반하면
안 된다는 법이라도 있나?
It's not.
그럴 리가 있나
여자라면 다 너한테 반하지
All the girls are attracted to you.
You're part bunny.
넌 새끼 토끼잖아
Mon, you want to come
see a movie with us?
모니카, 별일 없으면
우리랑 영화 보러 가자
실은 빨래가 좀 밀려서
Actually, I was going
to do some laundry.
Want to do it with me?
챈들러, 빨래 같이 할래?
Sure, I'll do it with you.
- 알았어, 그러지 뭐
- 그래
Okay, great.
Hold on a second.
잘됐다, 잠깐만
Here you go.
여기
괜찮지? 이 은혜는
절대 잊지 않을게
That would really help me out a lot.
Thanks.
You know what?
I don't have enough quarters.
난 동전이 부족한데
I have quarters!
나한테 있어
Great. Now we can do laundry all night.
All night laundry!
밤새 빨아도 되겠네
밤샘 빨래!
얘들아
Hey, any word on the apartment yet?
왔구나, 집은 어떻게 됐어?
알아봤는데 그 벌거숭이가
직접 세놓을 모양이더라
I called there, and it turns out
Naked Guy is subletting it.
He's already had 100 applicants.
- 지원자는 줄을 섰고
- 저런
-Oh, man.
-No, no, it's okay.
아냐, 괜찮아
Because you know what the difference
between them and me is?
내가 남들과 다른 게
뭔 줄 알아?
Your history of bedwetting?
결혼 실패 경력?
나 실망시키지 마
Hey, I trusted you, man!
Anyway, the difference is...
어쨌든 난 남들보다
유리한 위치에 있어
...I've got the edge.
It's not exactly ethical,
but I sent him a bribe...
도의에는 어긋나겠지만
뇌물로 기름칠을 좀 해뒀지
...to tip the scales in my direction.
아마 여기서도 보일 거야
You can see it from the window.
그래
활을 얹어놓은 핀볼기계야?
Is it that pinball machine
with the big bow on it?
아니
That new mountain bike?
그럼 저 산악자전거?
아니
뭘 보냈는데
What did you send?
A basket of mini muffins.
미니머핀 한 바구니
There's a whole table of them.
Which one did you send?
미니머핀 바구니가 잔뜩 있네
넌 어떤 걸 보냈는데
The small one.
아담한 거
You actually thought that basket
was going to get you the apartment?
정말 저 바구니 하나면
아파트가 생길 줄 알았니?
그럼
전에 박물관에도 미니머핀이
들어왔는데 정말 좋아하더라
Someone sent us a basket at work, and
people went crazy over those muffins.
It was the best day.
최고의 날이었지
Your work makes me sad.
난 서글퍼진다
Oh, man, I want that place so much!
젠장, 저 집에 꼭
들어가고 싶은데
And I was so sure
that was going to work.
저거면 먹힐 줄 알았어
There's 12 bucks
I'll never see again.
괜히 12달러만 날렸네
We'd better go if we want
to catch that movie.
- 이러다 영화 놓치겠다
- 그래
- 다녀와
- 안녕
Bye.
잘 있어, 챈들러
벌써 네가 그립다
Bye, Chandler.
I miss you already.
Did you see that? The inappropriate,
and the pinching?
너도 봤지?
방금 나 꼬집는 거?
Actually, I did.
그래, 봤어
이제 피비가 나한테
반했다는 말 믿겠어?
So do you believe
that she's attracted to me?
맙소사
Oh, my God!
She knows about us!
- 우리 관계를 아는 거야
- 정말 그럴까?
Are you serious?
우리 관계를 알고
골려주려는 거야
She knows, and she's trying
to freak us out!
That's the only explanation!
그렇게 밖엔 설명이 안 돼
But what about my pinchable butt
and my bulging biceps?
그럼 내 말랑한 엉덩이랑
차돌 같은 이두박근은?
She knows!
알고 있는 거야!
조이
왜?
Phoebe knows about us.
피비가 우리 관계를 알아
I didn't tell them!
난 걔들한테 말 안 했어
Them?
걔들? 걔들이라니
Who's "them"?
Phoebe and Joey.
피비랑 조이
조이
And Rachel.
그리고 레이첼
- 너희들한테 얘기하지 말랬어
- 맙소사
I would have told you,
but I promised not to tell.
미안해, 어쨌든
이제 다 끝났지?
I'm sorry.
But it's over now, right?
You can tell them you know they know,
and I can go back to knowing nothing!
걔들이 아는 걸
너희들이 아니까
이제 나만 아는 건
아무 것도 없어
Unless
- 하지만...
- 안 돼, 하지만이 뭐야
Not "unless"!
This must end now!
그만 끝내자니까
They think they are so slick
messing with us.
자기들만 똑똑한 줄 알겠지
But they don't know
that we know that they know.
하지만 걔들이 안다는 걸
우리가 안다는 걸 걔들은 몰라
So
- 그러니까...
- 그렇지
The messers become the messees!
이제 상황 대역전이다
Come on, you guys.
Think how much fun it would be to tell.
이러지 마, 그냥
말해도 재미있잖아
We know, we know, we know
다 안다, 다 알아, 안다고
What?
뭐?
Oh, that wasn't you.
참! 네가 아니었지
로스, 이제 그만 좀 해둬
Honey, you got to stop
torturing yourself.
차라리 다른 아파트를 찾아봐
Why don't you find another apartment?
이번 달에 아파트를
수도 없이 봤지만
I've already looked
at 1000 apartments this month.
None of them even compares
to that one.
저거랑은 비교가 안 돼
Well, except for one, but I would have had
to share it with an Armenian family.
딱 하나가 있긴 했는데
주인이랑 같이 사는 거라
Grandma really liked me.
그 집 할머니가 날 좋아하더라
But I want Ugly Naked apartment!
그래도 내겐 벌거숭이
아파트가 최고야
You know what?
방법 하나 알려줘?
You should find out his hobbies
and use that to bond with him.
저 사람 취미를 알아내서
친분을 쌓는 건 어때
Like if I wanted something from Joey...
그래, 내가 조이한테
원하는 게 있다면
...I would strike up a conversation
about sandwiches...
이런 주제로 대화를 하겠지
샌드위치
아니면 내 속옷
...or my underwear.
I'm listening.
계속해
봤지?
That is a great idea!
그거 좋은 생각이다
And I know Ugly Naked Guy because
we've been watching him for five years.
게다가 우린 5년 동안이나
벌거숭이를 봐왔기 때문에
So that gives me back my edge!
다시 유리한 위치를
점할 수 있어
Let's see now.
He had the trampoline.
- 트램폴린을 갖고 있었지?
- 그거 부서졌어
He broke that.
- 중력부츠도 있었고
- 그것도 망가뜨렸지
-He had gravity boots.
-He broke those too.
So he likes to break stuff.
물건을 부수는 취미라...
I've got to go pick up Ben.
But I will figure something out.
벤 데리러 가야 돼
좋은 방법이 있을 거야
Didn't he used to have a cat?
고양이도 키우지 않았나?
가슴 아픈 얘기니까
그 부분은 건드리지 마
I wouldn't bring that up.
It would bum him out.
불쌍한 녀석
엉덩이에 깔려죽다니
Poor cat never saw
that big butt coming.
여보세요
그럼, 기다려
여기 있어
Hold on a second,
she's right here.
챈들러야
It's Chandler.
Hello, you.
안녕, 그대
Phoebe, I've been thinking
about you all day.
나야, 피비
종일 네 생각만 했어
엥?
You know that thing you said before?
I was intrigued.
네 얘기에 관심이 없다면
거짓말이겠지
Really?
진짜?
Joey won't be here tonight.
오늘 조이 외박할 건데 와서
내 알통을 느껴보는 게 어때?
Why don't you come over?
I'll let you feel my bicep.
Or maybe more.
그 이상도 좋고
I'll have to get back to you on that.
다시 전화할게, 안녕
He wants me to come over
and feel his bicep and more!
나더러 자기 집에 와서
알통 이상을 느껴보래
Are you kidding?
- 진짜야?
- 그래
I cannot believe
he would do that to Mon
어쩜 그럴 수가...
조이? 우리가 안다는 걸
걔들이 아니?
Joey? Do they know that we know?
- 아니
- 조이!
They know you know.
- 너희들이 안다는 거 알아
- 그럴 줄 알았어
I knew it!
I would say, "Thank God!
Everybody knows! It's finally over!"
'신이여, 감사합니다
결국 다 끝났네요'
But that hasn't been working for me.
이건 정녕 꿈이런가
I cannot believe those two!
정말 웃기지도 않아
지금 우리한테
도전한다 이거야?
They thought they could mess with us?
Trying to mess with us?
They don't know that we know
they know we know.
걔들이 안다는 걸 우리가
안다는 걸 걔들은 몰라
Joey, you can't say anything.
- 넌 입 다물고 있어
- 말하고 싶어도 못하겠네
Couldn't if I wanted to.
Good evening, sir. I'm Ross Geller.
I'm one of the applicants.
안녕하세요, 선생님
저는 로스 겔러인데
입주신청자 중 한 명이죠
경쟁이 치열하다는 거
잘 알고 있습니다만...
I realize that the competition
is fierce but....
I'm sorry, I can't help but notice
that you're naked.
죄송한데 알몸이 자꾸
눈에 들어오는군요
I applaud you.
박수를 보냅니다
Man, I wish I was naked.
저도 벗고 싶네요
I mean, this looks so great.
너무나 멋지십니다
That is how God intended it.
이게 신의 뜻이겠죠
Look. They're panicked!
쟤들 좀 봐
완전히 쫄았어
- 곧 항복할 거야
- 그럼
They'll totally back down.
그래, 데이트를 원하면
데이트를 해주겠어
If he wants a date,
he's going to get a date.
I'm going to go in.
가볼게
좋아, 섹시하게
Be sexy.
Please.
너도 참...
I'd love to come by tonight.
챈들러, 오늘밤에 들를게
Really?
정말?
Absolutely.
Say, around 7?
물론이지, 7시쯤 어때?
좋지
I'm really looking forward to you
and me having sexual intercourse.
그래, 빨리 너랑
관계를 갖고 싶다
Hey, check it out!
얘들아, 저길 봐
Naked Guy's got a naked friend.
못난이 벌거숭이한테
벌거숭이 친구가 생겼어
진짜네?
엄마야, 쟤 우리 친구야!
Oh, my God!
That's our friend!
It's Naked Ross!
벌거숭이 로스!
Would you like another mini muffin?
미니머핀 더 드실래요?
오, 블루베리가 맛있어요
Try the blueberry, they're delicious.
Showtime!
결전의 순간이다
Rachel, get me perfume.
- 향수 좀 줘
- 알았어
Joey, can you get me
a bottle of wine and glasses?
조이, 넌 와인이랑
잔 좀 챙겨줄래?
All right, thanks, but glasses that do not
have handles and that are glass.
고맙긴 한데 잔은
손잡이가 없는 걸로
And wine that is not olive oil.
그리고 와인은
올리브오일 말고
Make her think you want to have
sex with her and it will freak her out.
잘해야 돼
진짜 같이 잘 것처럼 하면
걘 기겁할 거야
How far am I gonna have to go with her?
근데 어느 선까지 가야 되지?
She'll give in way before you do.
걱정 마, 시작도 하기 전에
항복할 테니
How do you know?
어떻게 알아?
Because you're on my team.
My team always wins.
넌 내 편이잖아
우리 편은 항상 이겨
At this?
이런 상황에서도?
Just go get some! Go!
가서 본때를 보여줘
어서!
- 난 여기서 엿듣고 있을게
- 그래
Now, I'm going to try to listen
from right here.
Oh, wait.
잠깐!
Good idea.
- 좋은 생각이야
- 그래, 잠시만
Don't give away the farm.
- 알맹이는 까지 마
- 알았어
피비
- 챈들러
- 들어와
Come on in.
I was going to.
그럴 작정이야
I brought some wine.
Would you like some?
와인 가져왔는데 마실래?
Sure.
좋지
So here we are.
여기까지 와버렸네
긴장되니?
Nervous?
Me? No. You?
나? 별로, 넌?
아니, 늘 바라던 일인 걸
I want this to happen.
So do l.
피차일반이야
I'm going to put on some music.
음악 들을래?
Joey likes to scare the duck.
조이가 오리 겁주는 소리야
Maybe I'll dance for you.
널 위해 출게
You look good.
멋지다
Thanks.
고마워
You know, when you say
things like that, it makes me...
저기...
네가 그런 말을
할 때면 난...
...want to rip that
sweater vest right off.
그 조끼를 확
찢어버리고 싶어
Why don't we move into the bedroom?
- 장소를 침실로 옮길까?
- 정말?
Really?
Do you not want to?
내키지 않아?
물론 아냐
First I want to take off
all my clothes...
내가 옷을 벗으면
온몸에 로션을 발라 줘
...and have you rub lotion on me.
That would be nice.
그거 좋은 생각이다
I'll go get the lotion.
로션 가져올게
It's way out of hand.
She wants me to put lotion on her!
일이 너무 커지고 있어
자기 몸에 로션을 발라 달래
-She's bluffing!
-She's not backing down.
허풍이야
물러날 것 같지 않아
막 이런다니까
She went like this
He's not backing down.
He went to get lotion.
물러설 것 같지 않아
지금 로션 가지러 갔어
It's Chandler. You can take him.
챈들러는 네 밥이잖아
Come on. Don't you remember when
you made him cry using only your words?
네 말 한마디에
질질 짜던 애라고
Aren't you guys done yet?
이런, 아직도 안 끝났냐?
I want to sit in my chair!
나 의자에 좀 앉자
The sooner Phoebe breaks him, the sooner
it's over and out in the open.
조이, 이렇게 생각해
피비가 챈들러를 이기면
완전히 상황 종료야
- 그거 괜찮은데?
- 그렇지
I like that.
그래, 맞다
브라를 보여줘
Show him your bra.
He's afraid of bras. Can't work them.
브라를 무서워하거든
You didn't rip off any buttons.
단추는 다 멀쩡하네
It's not my first time.
장사 한두 번 하냐?
Go back there and seduce her
till she cracks!
얼른 다시 나가서
항복 선언 받아내
잠깐만 기다려봐
Give me a second.
-Did you clean up in here?
-Of course!
- 너 여기 청소했냐?
- 당연하지
벌써 가려고?
You're going?
Not without you, lover.
널 두고 가진 않아, 내 사랑
So this is my bra.
어때...
내 브라야
It's very, very nice.
보기 좋다 야
Well, come here.
자, 이리 와
I'm very happy we're going
to have all the sex.
섹스 생각을 하니
너무 행복해
You should be.
I'm very bendy.
그렇겠지
나 엄청 유연하거든
I'll kiss you now.
이제 키스할 거야
Not if I kiss you first.
내가 할지도 몰라
I guess there's nothing
left for us to do but kiss.
이제 다른 수가 없군
키스를 해야겠어
Here it comes.
그럼 한다
Our first kiss.
우리의 첫 키스
그래, 알았어
네가 이겼다
You win!
- 너랑은 못 자
- 그건 왜?
I can't have sex with you!
-And why not?
-I'm in love with Monica!
난 모니카를 사랑하니까
뭐? 뭐라고?
You're what?
Love her!
사랑해, 그래
난 모니카를 사랑해
I love her!
난 모니카를 사랑한다고
I love you, Monica.
사랑해, 모니카
I love you too, Chandler.
나도 널 사랑해, 챈들러
I thought you were doing it.
I didn't know you were in love!
그냥 즐긴 게 아니라
사랑이었구나
Dude!
짜식들
Hats off to Phoebe.
Quite a competitor.
경의를 표한다, 피비
대단한 적수였어
May I say your breasts are still showing.
그리고 너 아직도 가슴 보인다
어머나
God.
All right!
So that's it?
좋아, 그럼 이제 끝이다
이제 다들 아네
It's over.
Everybody knows!
Actually, Ross doesn't.
아직 오빠는 모르지
We'd appreciate it
if no one told him yet.
로스한테는 당분간
비밀로 해주면 고맙겠다
Well, here it is.
바로 여깁니다
새 로스를 위한 새 집
A new place for a new Ross.
I'll have you and the guys from work
over, once it's furnished.
이사 마치면 박물관 식구들을
초대해서 집들이도 하려구요
It's nice to see you
back on your feet.
자네 본연의 모습으로
돌아와서 기쁘네
I am that, and the whole rage thing
is definitely behind me.
맞습니다, 이젠 제 감정을
충분히 다스릴 수 있습니다
I wonder if it's time for you
to rejoin our museum team?
자네의 복직을 제안하고 싶네만
That would be great.
그래주시면 고맙죠
당장이라도 일할 수 있습니다
I am totally ready
to come back to work.
뭐야, 안 돼
이게...
What are you doing?
무슨 짓이야!
Get off my sister!
내 동생 건드리지 마!